{
    "subject": "Sheldon_Reynolds__producer_",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Killer's_Carnival",
    "human_readable": "Sheldon Reynolds directed the film Killer's Carnival.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9120158553123474,
            "question": "Have you heard of any other films directed by Sheldon Reynolds besides Killer's Carnival?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8515217304229736,
            "question": "Who directed the film Killer's Carnival?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8090888261795044,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Sheldon Reynolds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8053948879241943,
            "question": "Is Sheldon Reynolds a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6768264174461365,
            "question": "Is Sheldon Reynolds known for directing horror films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6138035655021667,
            "question": "Can you list any films directed by Sheldon Reynolds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5150169730186462,
            "question": "What is the plot of Killer's Carnival?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4922071099281311,
            "question": "When was the film Killer's Carnival released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4082225561141968,
            "question": "Are there any actors who starred in Killer's Carnival?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34827056527137756,
            "question": "What genre is the film Killer's Carnival likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sheldon Reynolds directed the film Killer's Carnival.",
            "html": "yago_10321_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any actors who starred in Killer's Carnival?",
            "html": "yago_10321_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Killer's Carnival released?",
            "html": "yago_10321_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Killer's Carnival?",
            "html": "yago_10321_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10321_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* There is a mention of \"Sheldon Reynolds\" in document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10321/re-ranker-msmarco/135.txt and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10321/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt, but it does not explicitly mention that he directed the film \"Killer's Carnival\".\n* However, in document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10321/re-ranker-msmarco/135.txt and 54.txt, there is a mention of Sheldon Reynolds as a helmer (director) and producer behind the film \"Killer's Carnival\" among other works.\n\nTherefore, based on this information, I would say that:\n\n* The triple is: Sheldon Reynolds directed the film Killer's Carnival.\n* The output is: {'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Sheldon Reynolds directed the film Killer's Carnival.\" Specifically, the document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10321/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt` mentions that Alberto Cardone and Robert Lynn, alongside Sheldon Reynolds, directed \"Killer's Carnival\" (1966 Italy/France/Austria). Therefore, the statement is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}